=Love Actually S5=
(Previously)
(New round of choices)
(Again.)
(Those who didn't press it last time...)
(I hope we can see)
(our true selves.)
(Without hesitation.)
(I was kind of relieved.)
So sweet.
Really.
(I haven't found)
(my ideal partner yet.)
(I know)
(Xihui won't choose me.)
(The fact that she has a child)
(is stressful for me.)
(Be true to myself.)
(Be true to her.)
He's so annoying.
My heart nearly jumped out
of my chest just now.
I feel like crying.
(Who will you invite
to open your life profile?)
(I just want)
(to give this relationship)
(a chance, that's all.)
(The novelty has worn off.)
(It's over.)
(Life profile, re-opening)
(What does it mean?)
(A plot twist?)
Restores hair shaft protein
from the root.
Lasting resilience and shine
for three days.
This show is sponsored
by Pantene Pro-V Foam Shampoo.
Illuma HMO.
World-leading HMO innovations
bridging maternal immunity.
This show is sponsored by Illuma HMO.
Welcome, everyone.
You're watching
WeTV's self-produced
light-mature age
dating observation reality show
Love Actually S5.
Hello, everyone. I'm Chunye.
Let's welcome
all the friends
in the observation room.
Welcome, Ms. Shen Yifei.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome, Ms. Evonne Sie.
Welcome, Guang.
That shows the age difference.
What was that?
Next,
let's welcome Guangzhi
back to the observation team.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you.
I'm back again.
You can't be on the same show
with him now?
With Zhisheng?
Yeah.
We avoid each other.
So serious
while talking nonsense.
It will be
the last 48 hours
in the Love House.
Do you have
any expectations
for the couples?
I'm more concerned
about Guangzhi's love story.
Is it still going on?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Then I'm good.
Honestly,
I'm full of anticipation.
But I'm most excited
about Zhou Youling and Liu.
Liu-Zhou duo.
The bossy CEO and innocent girl.
Yeah.
I caught up
on the previous episodes
and noticed some plot twists.
So I came
to see how it went.
So let's find out
what happened at the house
under the confession countdown.
Let's watch the clips.
It's over?
Why don't we go out in the rain too?
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Go ahead.
Put on a jacket. Let's walk in the rain.
I really like the grass after the rain.
It becomes more crisp.
Yeah.
I really like the smell.
Me too.
The lake.
So pretty.
(I think
Danqi is sorting out her feelings.)
Don't you think the sky after the rain
is like an oil painting?
There's a kite here.
During the interview
on the first day,
they asked
what kind of partner I was looking for.
(Chen Danqi's idea of love)
If it were to be described
with an image,
I hope I could be
a kite.
(He is the one holding the string.)
(There is a thin line connecting us.)
When we are in motion,
we head forward together.
Otherwise,
we dock at a place
to rest.
Now, with hope,
look at this image again.
I hope I am a lonely island.
He rows a boat to find me.
This fits with what you just said.
That's true.
I want to watch the sunset
(Jia Peixuan's idea of love)
and take a walk
with my partner on a mountaintop
or by the sea.
(I prefer)
(a relationship with mutual support)
(and steady, enduring affection.)
You're so handsome.
You're so pretty.
You're so handsome, it startled me.
("You're so handsome, it startled me.")
(Nice.)
(I'll tell my husband.)
(They really look like)
(they're married.)
(Wang Yi's idea of love)
I'm looking forward
to a sweet romance.
This is my original aspiration.
No matter how old I am,
it will never change.
Ribbit, ribbit.
The two frogs are back.
Hi.
Anyone there?
Maybe they're in the recreation room.
Do you push it like this?
Hi.
Why are you here all alone?
What are you doing?
I'm
working on something.
Doing a task.
(We're familiar with this path)
Just push.
How?
Let's not talk.
Why can't I push it?
You need to stand here.
Push here.
You can't stand on top of that.
You can't push yourself.
I was standing over there.
(Warmhearted citizen Ms. Wang)
Sorry.
It's okay.
Put some force.
No. Go away.
Okay.
Got to mute, sorry.
Time to eat.
Let's go eat.
(Mission accomplished)
They are checking the profiles today.
That's scary.
She will check the profile?
Yeah.
(Jia Peixuan, Xiao Wentao)
I think
Wentao has to
make up his mind
to open up.
(Ling Lizheng checks
Yang Xihui's life profile)
My idea of love.
(Yang Xihui's idea of love)
Progress together.
Get better and better.
(Zhou Youling and Xu Lvyang
check each other's life profiles)
(I want us)
(to move forward together,)
(keep learning,)
(Xu Lvyang's idea of love)
and explore the world.
I hope that we will always
have a lot to talk about.
I want us to be able
to chatter away at any time.
I want us to really
get each other.
I hope
that we are each other's best friends.
(I think I'd prefer to take it slow.)
(Just slowly.)
(Step by step.)
(Message Episode 9)
Take an exclusive note.
I put on makeup today.
Okay.
I hear someone screaming.
Yeah.
(Human nature)
(Walls have ears)
(This is sweet, guaranteed)
So sudden.
Random kisses.
I don't even know
what they're listening to.
That's something.
Let's go.
We can take an exclusive note.
We can ask them to leave.
Ask them to chat outside for a while.
We can take some photos.
Be careful. Is it heavy?
Not really.
(20 minutes later)
Want to go for a walk?
Yeah, put on a jacket.
(The photo booth crew is back)
The photo booth crew.
It won't work.
Even the fire brigade
couldn't open the door.
It won't work.
My neck is so sore.
Should we stay here?
Let's knock.
I'll tell them
we want to take some photos.
They're having a private chat.
You want photos?
Tomorrow.
We'll come back later.
Give them another twenty minutes.
They're having a serious talk.
The photos can wait.
Do you hear them?
Another serious talk.
Then...
(Human nature)
I won't just tell anyone.
Why are these two always eavesdropping?
They've settled down.
A lot of time at hand.
Yeah.
There's no room for us.
Let's go for a walk.
Do you really think I left?
Yeah, I thought you'd left.
I wouldn't be surprised
if you left.
I'm surprised you pressed the button.
She means the opposite.
Why are you hmph-ing?
(15 minutes ago, Jia Peixuan
read Xiao Wentao's life profile)
Want to go out?
I'm fine either way.
What are you doing?
Reading this.
Come on.
Let's go to your place.
My place is messy.
Alright.
You're done?
Yeah.
Any thoughts?
Thoughts?
It's basically what you told me.
Any differences?
Not really.
Yeah.
I just find it funny.
What?
Unstable income.
Yeah.
(Performances: 2000-3000 yuan per show)
Why are you so meticulous?
(Band: 2000-10000 yuan per show)
What can I do?
(Collaboration: 1000-3000 yuan per hour)
They asked about my income.
It could be an estimate.
I wrote my annual income.
My annual income is
zero.
It hasn't been a year yet.
How would I know my annual income?
He just graduated.
A newcomer
to the workforce.
He listed his income
in great detail.
(Every penny counts)
Every performance.
(All earned by himself)
(Many a little makes a mickle)
Every lesson.
"Why don't you make it vague?
Just the annual income."
He said,
"I've been back for half a year.
I don't have an annual income
for now."
This kid is too honest.
(Sincerity wins every time.)
Then I thought,
(Struck)
"This guy is quite cute."
Guangzhi, I'm curious
about your annual income.
It's unstable.
I'm just like Xiaowen.
This one.
This one is really cute.
(I know I'm cute)
What?
(Love myself)
Your photo?
You're falling
into narcissism again?
Of course.
I look so cute.
I'll take a picture of it.
Don't move.
I'll take another picture for you.
You're recording again.
I've recorded it.
Seriously.
Your red pants.
I'm really speechless.
These pants are awesome.
Don't they look good?
(Wearing red, never poor in life)
So cool.
I'm speechless.
Sometimes,
seeing your partner's childhood photos
makes you wish
you'd known them since that time.
Yeah, I love his childhood photos.
Yeah.
My profile is boring.
Nothing exciting.
Whose is exciting?
Mine?
It is.
So annoying.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
Seriously.
Yeah.
It feels that Xiaowen
is opening up.
Yeah.
Being able to joke around is great.
And they can talk.
That is a very good sign.
So you planned it all
and did it on purpose?
You thought I would just leave, right?
You did it on purpose?
No.
I just wanted to see your reaction.
You're so annoying.
I noticed when I got there.
(Clear vision)
Their room
(was directly facing the spot.)
(I had decided)
(to press the button.)
(But I pretended to leave.)
(I wanted to see her reaction.)
(Still at the playful age)
(Satisfied)
He also fooled us.
(It's all part of the play)
You thought I left.
But I came back.
(Toying with everyone)
You're so annoying.
I'm really speechless.
You did well.
Let me give you a painting.
Okay, give it to me.
Let me see.
It's downstairs.
Let's go downstairs.
Didn't she tear it?
Did she draw it again?
Xiaowen is smiling so much
that he has dimples.
He's even developed dimples
from the smiles.
What is this?
I saw it in the mirror.
You drew it?
Yeah.
What did I miss?
Just doodling.
You are such a talented
painter.
I can see it in the mirror.
I'm admiring it.
It's so good.
(Look at them)
So beautiful.
Do you know what the first one is?
Rapeseed flowers.
The rapeseed flowers from that day.
Let me take a half-body shot,
your legs included.
She drew
several classic scenes
from their memories.
That sunset.
She might have drawn it again.
The second is the day of surfing.
Surfing.
Yeah.
So cool.
So nice.
Fall in love.
Really.
♪When you look back and smile♪
The third one is...
If you guess it,
I'll give you a big reward.
I bet you can't.
There's a reward?
So many tricks.
♪The melody starts lightly♪
♪But the ending is so sweet♪
What's the last one?
The third painting.
I haven't figured out what it is yet.
It's all greenish.
I don't get it.
I want to guess first.
That would be more interesting.
The third painting
is from the evening
of the invitation day.
The tree seen from the balcony
(Invitation)
and the wind.
Wentao, you're so lucky.
♪You are the brightest chorus
in my alt account♪
(I'm happy.)
(Of course.)
(It means)
these three things
left a deep impression on her.
All these things
happened between us.
I want to...
What are you doing?
I'll keep it here
to show
everyone.
You're so...
(Take a look)
(Keep recording)
You're so sneaky.
(Jia Peixuan filming)
(He stuck it there.)
(Take a look.)
You're unhinged.
He's so cute.
I can't take it anymore.
(Special exhibition spot)
Swag.
So cool.
(Steadiness of a 24-year-old)
What are you doing?
Steadiness of a 24-year-old.
I'm showing the painting.
Showing the painting?
Showing the hips.
(Showing the world)
Just showing off.
Why wouldn't I show off?
I'm really speechless.
(Wentao losing it)
Hello.
What's that style?
Maybe love really makes people younger.
Have you become younger?
I have.
She would be so happy.
So happy.
Very fulfilling.
Yeah.
It works better than praising it.
You drew it here, right?
What board did you use?
This one?
Last time, I didn't draw so well.
Last time?
The one you tore.
The one you brought back.
(Bringing up Wentao's sad memories)
I brought it back.
Yeah.
Didn't I tell you
what I wrote
on the back of the painting?
After you brought it back,
I wrote something on it.
You didn't give it to me.
I tore it up
after you read my life profile
and talked to me.
Seeing those words
at that moment
would make you
even more lost.
It would only confuse you.
I didn't want to
cause either of us any burden.
Where did you throw it?
(Try to salvage it)
In the trash can.
Has the trash been emptied?
Of course.
Why are you hmph-ing?
He wants to piece it together?
No way.
He wants to.
If I hadn't read
that life profile,
you were planning
to give me that painting, right?
If you read that profile
and showed
a different state,
I might have given it to you.
But your state
was actually very normal.
I totally understand.
At that moment, I felt
that I was silly.
There was no need to be like that.
But at that moment,
I just wanted
to give us a chance.
So I pressed the button.
But when I learned
about your decision,
I did feel
a bit upset
deep down.
I asked myself
why I had to be like this?
I thought about it.
But I had no choice.
I really didn't want to do it.
Yeah, be honest with yourself.
He's sincerely expressing himself.
Yeah.
When I saw
those few lines of words,
I just felt
that they were too cold.
I really didn't like them.
At that time,
what I understood was
that if I chose to press the button,
we'd sort of
start dating.
I said this is simply impossible.
I didn't think at that time
that as we continued the recording,
I would enter a romantic relationship
with you.
It's just that everyone
has a different understanding
of these words
and a different way
of thinking about them.
The understanding is different.
I think it actually shows
Wentao is really a very cautious person.
He's very cautious.
He's treating this matter
very seriously.
So today, when I went again,
I remembered it was
the exact same paper,
the exact same words.
When I saw it today, I felt
I should follow my own understanding
to interpret these words.
So taking the photo today means
I hope I can
continue to interact
with the other person.
But when you were in Hainan,
you didn't have this idea.
When I was in Hainan,
I didn't fully understand.
my thought at that time was
I would definitely
continue to interact with you.
- But...
- It's definitely not a romantic relationship.
Definitely impossible.
You couldn't either.
But no one...
I think maybe except for BK
and Ruita,
no others
can possibly enter
a romantic relationship.
This is too far-fetched.
Too fast.
Yeah.
And we haven't interacted in real life
about some issues.
My spot
is a perfect spot for gossiping.
You know?
Then Danqi came.
Danqi said in my room...
She said, "I think you're like a mom."
I said yes.
I do have a child.
Then what did she say?
She didn't say anything.
I felt she wasn't shocked or surprised.
She just naturally took it in stride.
So she only found out today?
She only found out today.
What I'm really worried about is
that you will, because
of having to tell these things...
You can't
completely block out those
not quite normal...
They will definitely,
because of your past,
write some
really unpleasant words about you.
Do you get what I mean?
Have you been thinking about this issue?
I'm afraid
these things will bring you pressure.
You're worried about this?
Yes, of course.
You think so much.
He is starting to think for her.
So thoughtful.
She will feel that he thought of her.
This matter,
actually, has nothing to do with you.
I know.
But you can't
completely block out
those unpleasant words.
I'm worried
that when you see these things,
you'd feel pressured.
Yeah.
Actually, you know what?
The first moment
you finished telling me,
I thought
about how I can help you
to
hide this matter.
Really?
Wentao is so thoughtful.
(He told me)
he started to worry
about whether I would be hurt.
I was stunned.
At that moment, I was moved inside.
Inside, I was both touched
and surprised.
Although he's younger than me,
at that moment, in front of me,
he actually
wanted to give me a shoulder
and to help me with the burden.
At that moment, I was a bit
unable to organize my words
to say it out.
I just looked at him.
I just said
about these...
You don't have to transfer
these pressures
onto yourself.
This is something I should face.
Then he said,
"That won't work.
I just think about these things."
So actually, it's kind of mutual
between us.
Sometimes, I also tend
to overthink.
I wanted to...
You don't need to think about these
for me, actually.
(You'd really be touched.)
When you aren't even feeling sorry
for yourself yet,
someone already started
to feel sorry for you.
And he has always stood by her side,
never once standing against Xuan.
Yeah.
He wouldn't say,
"It's okay,
I'll be with you."
He wouldn't say those lukewarm words.
Yeah.
How is it?
What about what?
A kid preaching big truths.
Here we go again.
Seriously.
Where is this from?
What is this?
I don't know.
I feel like you'll have a lot more memes
in the future.
Oh, no.
You, in front of me,
are becoming more and more like a child.
I'll hold back.
No need.
I'll hold back a bit.
It's nice like this.
You...
I still can't just be myself.
It's nice like this.
Who drew this?
You drew this too?
Danqi drew it.
Why is it so heavy?
But this is...
Is it still wet?
It's been two days.
It's probably drying slowly.
Xiaowen.
You big kid.
Don't...
Go do something nice.
I'll stay away from you.
(I think Wentao is a kid
on the outside,)
but he is with an old soul.
But actually, I think Xuan,
although she's older than him,
her heart is super girly.
A little girl.
They're the opposite.
Yeah.
They really complement each other.
Xuan,
what are you doing?
Reading.
Is that pillow you're holding
Illuma HMO?
As a mom, I know this brand too.
It's very reassuring.
Really? What a coincidence.
HMO has been really popular lately.
All my mom friends are talking about it.
Look at this
newly launched Illuma Initial.
It contains seven key HMOs.
Two of them can be seen directly
on the ingredient list.
It's genuinely added in high amounts.
Moms who know HMO choose Illuma HMO.
Such a great choice, as expected of you.
- Hello.
- Hi, you're back.
Want some? Have you eaten?
- A little.
- Want some?
It's okay, I've eaten.
What are you eating?
Meat pie, it's very delicious.
- Break off a bite.
- You eat.
This is that.
Finish eating, then I'll chat with you.
Chat with you for a bit.
Okay.
(Ji Yu still has something to say)
I'll go talk to Ji Yu.
He wants to talk to me.
Okay, go ahead.
You want a cucumber, right?
I'm not eating anymore.
(So pitiful.)
Ji Yu said, "Can I talk to you?"
She went to tell him
she'd go talk to him.
Talk for a bit.
Do you want a cucumber?
Ji Yu got hurt again.
What are you drinking?
I'm drinking jasmine white tea.
- Okay.
- Where to talk?
- It's really delicious.
- In that room.
Okay.
How was it? Did you have fun?
It was okay.
Okay, have a seat.
What's up?
I just still feel really happy
to know you.
Me too.
I feel like we both
came in on the last day.
And you see, on the first day,
I saw
your graceful appearance.
Later on,
you revealed some soft parts
to me.
I just think,
although there's no such thing
as complete empathy,
I can always tell
right way many
of your emotional shifts.
I noticed it.
I just feel
that you're like
another version of me in the world.
He made her cry.
Anyway, I really do hope
you can be happy.
I think if you're dating Lizheng,
I'd also be very happy.
I hope he is able to give you happiness
and the strength
to resist the dire reality.
If not,
I still hope you can know
if you ever need any help,
you have
a strong friend
who is able to lift you up.
If you ever need any help,
you can always come to me.
Really.
Well, I
(Ji Yu chooses to leave the Love House)
will be leaving the show.
He is leaving?
I feel like I can't
calmly
watch someone I might have feelings for
or care about
be intimate with someone else
in front of me.
Plus, I don't want to use
superficial open-mindedness
to disguise my inner care.
I think I know my personality well.
So I just
really respect your choice.
Ji Yu is really mature.
Very decent, very mature.
Hui, I'm drawn to her.
Undoubtedly, you are a great beauty.
Would you like to partner with me again?
Sure.
Thank you.
(Hui.)
If you have time,
let's go out and hang out.
If you don't have other plans.
Okay.
No.
(Fate is hard to say.)
(Sometimes, it goes around in circles.)
This needs to be put in the fridge.
Did you only ask me out yesterday,
or did you invite everyone?
Only you.
(Ji Yu just makes you
feel sorry for him.)
Don't.
(I invited her to go to Hangzhou
with me yesterday.)
Today, I heard
she's going to Xiamen with someone else,
So I quietly lowered my head.
Were you a bit sad then?
(Actually, they already have)
(a partner
with whom they've progressed.)
(When my chances were cut off,)
(I feel that staying here)
(is no longer necessary.)
(I don't want to give others)
(any trouble or burden.)
(He is really sincere.)
I want to tell her honestly
about me leaving
and why.
I hope she can know
what I'm thinking.
I'm really
afraid of having no sense of boundaries
or burdening others.
I don't want to put others
in a difficult position.
So I hope
you can look after yourself well
and take care.
This is so sudden.
I just think you're...
First of all, indeed, we two
entered the house on the same day.
So I feel like we're
naturally like
comrade-in-arms.
I just think you're
without any pretense,
a very simple and direct person.
That day when I went out
on a date with you,
I really could feel
no matter
how I look,
it'd just be fine.
I just felt really happy.
Like friends, Ji Yu is like her friend.
It's like between buddies,
you can look very ugly.
I told you that day...
I said, "Who says a guy and a girl
can't just be good friends?"
Between us, there is
the feeling of being
very comfortable together.
Of course.
Ji Yu is too considerate and too good.
They've become friends, buddies.
Actually, Ji Yu's personal charm
had no chance
to shine here.
But I really think
even after the show, with Ji Yu,
we can still be good friends.
I hope you get better and better.
For sure.
Okay?
Be happy.
- Take care.
- Take care, you take care too.
You'll definitely get better and better.
Take good care.
There's a long road ahead.
Yes, the house is just the beginning.
Yeah.
Please just explore with your heart
and develop.
Let everything go naturally.
Don't have any burdens in your heart.
Love boldly
and experience everything bravely.
Okay?
When are you leaving tomorrow?
I haven't told everyone yet.
I want to tell them tomorrow, or...
I wanted to talk to you first.
It's a bit too late today,
and many people are already asleep.
Tomorrow, I can
cook a meal with everyone
and dine with them.
Yeah, not too sudden.
- Right.
- Not too sudden.
I'll head back first.
I think being on the same wavelength
is very important.
Yes, it's just that in the house,
I don't think there is anyone
really suitable for him.
Just wasn't there, no fated one.
(The next day)
(Tonight...)
(Let's...)
(Raise a glass together.)
(Yes.)
Come on.
All the best.
Ji Yu.
Cheers.
We'll probably see each other again
in a few days.
Cheers.
If you need anything over there,
I'll help you get it.
Otherwise, you can't reach it.
I'll get you some.
You take your chopsticks.
We can go get the gifts.
Even bought a cake.
Bought a cake.
I hope in your own moon,
you find your own love and happiness.
I'm grateful.
That's for sure.
The flower language
of Phalaenopsis is beauty,
happiness, and luck.
May your future
have countless things like Phalaenopsis
happening in your life, alright?
Look at what I wrote for you.
It's beautiful.
(To Ji Yu: Spring breeze, rain, spring scenery, and morning light, you)
So beautiful.
So good at drawing.
The next stage is to look up.
- Yes.
- Well said.
Well said.
Everyone is so talented.
Really.
Four seasons of rainbow,
gentle rain and breeze.
- Ji Yu.
- Did you write this?
I wrote it, and there's my seal.
(Originally, I thought
it was quite ordinary,)
(like eating together.)
But when everyone bought me a cake
and gave me gifts,
I slowly got that feeling of separation.
Separation is the hardest.
Look at me.
Here, look at me.
Three, two, one.
Look at me.
Look at what Wentao drew for me.
It's drawn so well.
To Xingren, may your life be bright.
This is really well drawn.
Was this created just now?
Just created.
Thank you, Wentao.
Come on, take a photo of me and Ji Yu.
- Come on.
- Where's my coupon?
You threw it away, right?
(The gift from this afternoon)
This is for you.
What's this?
I drew it.
Thank you.
Open it.
Little tiger.
Twice.
- Free hosting.
- Okay.
Xihui, being open and natural.
Can I see?
Just take a look like this.
You can't touch.
- Come on.
- Come on, bro.
Take a photo.
Okay.
They're lining up to take photos
with you, my friend.
So nice.
Next.
Mascot.
With my roommate.
Handsome.
- Next.
- Handsome.
We've experienced together
what I think is
a very precious half month in life.
I think it was
a very wonderful experience.
Hello, everyone.
Ji Yu.
Yeah. You can also call me Xingren.
Xingren.
Yes.
Nice to meet you all.
Will no one choose me?
(Although I'm very regretful)
(I didn't establish)
(a certain relationship here,)
(our friendship has been established.)
Wait for me.
(I think this kind of friendship,)
(in this current era,)
(is very rare.)
(We have no work connections.)
(We became friends
just because of you yourselves.)
(I think it's really rare.)
I'm very happy.
I think meeting everyone
is just so happy.
I think meeting everyone is
a very happy thing.
We'll meet again.
We'll definitely meet again.
We'll see each other again.
Let's hug.
We must.
Relax.
Okay?
Let's take turns hugging him.
Take turns hugging him.
Hug me.
Roommate, my roommate.
(Group living is healing.)
Goodbye.
(I hope all the friends in the house)
(can find themselves here)
(and the other half who
understands you in those moments.)
(I want to say to Hui)
that I hope you always have someone
who understands you in those moments.
(Ji Yu is a very stable guy.)
He totally knows what he wants
and needs.
Mixed emotions.
Yes, every time Love Actually enters
the countdown,
it always makes people feel
so many emotions.
Just now when Danqi and Xuan
were chatting,
they saw
a very beautiful kite outside the house.
Then Danqi described to her
her ideal relationship
was somehow like
flying a kite.
Each of you,
based on your preferences,
please describe your ideal love.
What would it look like?
I think the sweetest love is
that after everything is done,
you still have the energy
to fall in love.
You love this person
for who they are.
I just hope
we can give each other some support,
heal each other,
and make progress together.
But if we regress together,
just don't blame me.
(You can rephrase)
What is this?
It means after we regressed together,
(Regression)
just don't...
We shouldn't leave each other.
(But don't leave)
Don't dislike each other.
It means after I regressed,
I hope you can be my safety net.
Don't leave me.
Otherwise, I'd always have
the pressure to always improve.
I'm very afraid of this.
(Let me help you phrase it)
When Guangzhi said "regress," does he mean...
For example,
if my career reaches a peak,
- it will ultimately go downslope.
- Yes.
Not that I become a worse person.
I might have a worse figure.
I might get fat.
But I don't think
this is called regression, actually.
This counts too, right?
This is the body getting out of shape.
After your interpretation,
I feel even worse.
I'd rather...
My ideal relationship
might not be so passionate,
nor so poetic.
It's more like
daily necessities.
Very plain,
but it can paint a splendid world.
It can also be made into
a delicious dish.
Beautiful.
This month, he seems
to have experienced a lot.
No, it's just...
Just this month,
the whole experience was a growth.
It's from watching
dating variety shows, right?
Thanks to Love Actually.
It brought me to semi-maturity.
The more you watch, the maturer you get.
I can understand.
I think it's a big hand
and a small hand in front.
It means no matter what,
it's simple
and being together.
No matter what,
I think as long as they are together,
it's fine.
But I don't think
ideal love means having to
be together or whatever.
Because all human emotions
are related to your early
intimate experiences.
A newborn baby
and his parents
will definitely go through three stages.
First is called "hold me tight."
When the baby is just born,
he really needs to be held tight.
Then it's "put me down."
I want to walk independently.
Finally, it's "leave me alone."
I want to do my own things.
Leave me alone.
I think a good love
actually has all three stages.
What matters is our rhythm.
For example, when I want
to be held tight,
you can be there and hold me tight.
When I want to put myself down,
we can be like kites,
each doing our own things.
And when we need solitude,
we can respect each other's
space for solitude.
I think this is a very good form
of a good love.
Yeah.
Last episode, through
opening the life profiles,
we heard for the first time
some stories
from Liu (Xu Lvyang)'s childhood.
I don't know if everyone had,
in your growth process,
the experience
of seeking others' approval.
Or
your insights and feelings.
I remember when I was in high school,
as the graduate representative,
I gave a speech on behalf of the school.
Actually, I usually had
various performances,
and I never
asked my parents to come watch.
But that day, I suddenly
wanted them to come and see
how amazing I was.
So when I
finished the very well-written speech
and everyone was applauding me
and screaming,
I saw my parents just coming in.
But I found that at that moment,
I wasn't disappointed.
Because I felt I had gotten
what I wanted.
I was speaking
to these audience members.
This is a very cute experience.
I'm actually the same.
My mom is also not very good at
giving compliments.
I couldn't get
positive feedback from my mom.
The impact on me later was
that in my later work,
I wasn't used to
seeking others' opinions.
I liked to bury myself in work.
This way, my work efficiency
is very low.
I have a question.
(Excuse me)
Were you also someone
who couldn't compliment?
Yes.
From about 24 years old,
I started to learn
how to compliment others.
You have to accept others'
praise and compliments toward you.
(Still learning)
I'm practicing.
You have to feel that I'm worthy.
Yes, I want to receive praise.
(Learned something)
Okay.
What about Guang?
I'm actually similar
to Liu (Xu Lvyang).
Our
upbringing environment
might also be the same.
I also learned many, many things.
It was also because of my mom's
expectations for me.
So I've always had a fixed mindset
that I hoped that everything I did
would get others' approval.
When I grew up, I realized belatedly
this desire deviated from my true will.
But actually, this is wrong.
Others' happiness
doesn't come from your happiness.
Don't place your happiness
on others either.
Find some approval
and happiness from yourself.
Well said.
In our research, we often say
that for the approval
of the person you need to value,
the person should stand in your future.
The key is,
if you've actively chosen
whose approval
is important to you.
Have those people stood
in your future?
If you figure it out,
you can both
make some adjustments
to get others' approval,
but at the same time you won't
be drained of a lot of energy.
So it's about choosing
a person who will stand in your future.
But in the plot just now,
in Hui's future,
Ji Yu probably won't appear.
What do you all think about Ji Yu
choosing to leave the house?
I think it's great.
In semi-maturity,
there's no time to waste.
- Yes.
We often say
that so-called emotional relationships
are pure relationships,
which is the best.
I think our house
seems to have invisibly
created such a
testing ground for pure relationships.
Even though Ji Yu, in the end,
didn't gain
the one he originally expected,
he still gained a lot
of pure relationships.
These pure relationships
might be friends
or partners who can help each other
in the future.
I think that's a very good experience.
I think
this deep interaction
with a high-quality group
is very healing for a person.
So I think this house
for all the male and female guests
coming here
is very, very important.
And I think
Ji Yu is a very sensitive
boy.
So when many people chat with him,
they naturally say to him
many heartfelt words.
So I think such a
very sensitive boy
in real life
will definitely meet someone
who likes him very much,
loves him, and understands him.
We also wish Ji Yu
can welcome a better love life
outside the Love House.
Understood.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Go to my place?
So soon?
(Yes.)
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Aren't your parents home?
Will your parents go out?
No, they won't.
That's so fast.
Meeting the parents is quite stressful.
Oh my god.
Go home and cook a meal.
Am I cooking?
We'll cook. I'll cook.
Your parents are there.
And the dog is there.
And the cat is there.
(But I think some girls)
(would feel too nervous
and think it's too fast.)
(Meeting the parents
before we even start dating.)
You should have told me earlier.
Now it's already
eleven o'clock.
You're not being a good friend.
You should have
told me as soon as you got back
and said, "Liu (Xu Lvyang),
come home with me tomorrow."
Then I wouldn't have eaten
so much tonight.
(I felt it was too sudden.)
(I was totally unprepared.)
I didn't expect
that in such a short time,
I would go to his home
to meet his parents first.
I went completely blank at that moment.
I was extremely nervous.
At a loss all of a sudden.
But I didn't prepare anything.
Don't need to buy any gifts.
That would be so impolite.
Let me think.
Or we can go out shopping
together tomorrow.
Just buy something casually.
It's already a bit tight on time.
I'll talk to them.
Come home with me tomorrow.
Mission guaranteed.
(I want to bring
Liu (Xu Lvyang) home because)
(now we've entered this stage.)
(To let her know me)
more deeply and truly,
I want to take her home
for a quick visit
to the legendary blue home.
The first time we met,
that fated card drawn.
(Your favorite colors are both blue. You decorated the house blue.)
(She can't take her eyes off blue clothes.)
The card also mentioned
that the home was decorated in blue.
And also,
my parents are also relatively
open-minded
and quite easygoing.
In a relatively relaxed state,
we'll meet them. Yeah.
It's not that kind of very formal,
very serious meeting.
(The next morning)
Are you ready?
Almost ready.
Let me see what you're wearing today.
You're so casual today.
And I'm dressed so formally.
Today I'm dressed very preppy.
(Passing by)
What does my formal outfit count as?
It's not like I'm meeting the parents.
But Liu (Xu Lvyang) should be happy.
She received from Youling
something about this relationship...
Because it means taking it seriously.
He wants to be very formal with you.
- Yes.
- That's right.
As expected, someone
who wants to be favored
is also someone who shows favoritism.
Because if you have to choose
between meeting the parents quickly
and refusing to let you meet
the parents no matter what,
meeting the parents quickly is better.
(Going home)
You're dressed so ladylike today.
Am I not ladylike normally?
Normally...
Does it look good,
this outfit today?
It looks good.
Let's go.
Where's the dog?
Over there. The dog is over there.
Then I'll sit inside.
I seem to have frozen up.
So nervous.
This is nervous happiness.
These hands haven't been apart since.
- What for?
- Good luck.
Easier said than done.
Indeed, easier.
Still scared.
Almost there, but still a bit scared.
My heart is beating so fast.
It'll be fine once we go up.
We're here.
(Going home)
You just climbed down first.
Brother says he's been away for a month.
He can finally go home.
Let me carry this.
(Zhou Youling's parents)
(Surprise)
It's too sudden.
(An unexpected meeting)
I felt embarrassed myself,
not to mention Liu (Xu Lvyang).
Because I thought after we went inside,
they would be inside the house.
I didn't expect them to be standing
at the door waiting.
Yes, it was a bit formal.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Zhou.
Hello, pretty girl.
Her name is Liu (Xu Lvyang).
Liu (Xu Lvyang), right?
Yes,
my full name is Xu Lvyang,
and you can call me Liu (Xu Lvyang).
Liu (Xu Lvyang), right? Okay.
Xu with the double person radical.
Okay, come in.
(My first impression at that time was)
(that it matched what Youling)
said before.
Just by looking at their faces,
I can tell they were amiable and kind.
Two very approachable elders.
Should she wear
those nice-looking slippers?
I think these slippers
are uncomfortable.
It's okay.
Wear this pair.
This pair is more comfortable.
Thank you, Mrs. Zhou.
I just happen to have a pair.
You can change into these.
They look very nice.
These are too big.
They're uncomfortable for you to wear.
Thank you.
So attentive.
Mrs. Zhou is too thoughtful.
A pretty girl wearing
pretty little slippers.
Okay, let's go in.
This matches a bit better.
They fit perfectly.
Right? They fit perfectly.
Although I was shocked
at the moment of meeting them
and felt it was very sudden,
actually, maybe
after a brief exchange,
I could feel that his parents
are actually easy to get along with.
They are very approachable.
This yellow phalaenopsis.
- Yes.
- Beautiful.
I've never seen this before.
He really grew up in a loving family.
The first thing Mrs. Zhou said
was to compliment her as pretty.
I've never seen this before.
This is a gift for you both.
Thank you very much.
(We don't stand on ceremony)
We have nothing special, just casual.
It's fine.
And this is also for you.
These are all health supplements.
Thank you.
Are you cold wearing that?
- No, I'm not cold.
- Okay.
We'll
cook a meal in a bit.
You guys just rest.
What?
Don't we need to keep them company
for a while?
No need.
(You guys retreat first)
You go upstairs and feed Brother,
or take him for a walk.
(Mom understands)
(Dad will pack himself up and leave)
Then we'll go upstairs first. Okay.
First, he sent his parents away.
His parents are at a loss.
Look at their expressions.
Then take this flower upstairs too.
Is it easy to carry?
- Yes, easy to carry.
- It's okay.
Easy to carry.
Anyway, we'll call you
when it's time to eat.
Okay.
I felt a bit awkward at the time.
If we sat down to chat immediately
upon meeting,
it would feel a bit rigid too.
I just think maybe it's better
to relax since we just arrived.
(Home now, make yourself comfortable.)
You don't need to take off your coat.
Well done.
Let's take a look around first.
(We're in my comfort zone now)
Let me show you around.
Okay.
This is the living room.
Here's a karaoke room.
This is where I play video games.
Here is a...
Swimming pool.
For bathing.
It's really all blue.
Yes.
He loves blue way too much.
Just look.
Well.
Look at the color.
This water, the lights,
and that wall are a gradient blue.
Isn't it?
And this too.
This is also blue marble.
And these lights too.
Because I noticed this light
will reflect your slippers
and make them look blue too.
Yes.
Look at this blue.
The blue of this floor
is rarely used.
It looks good.
It just has a kind
of beach-like feeling.
Yes.
I was about to say
it's like ocean waves.
This is
a small sitting area in my bedroom.
And here is a...
Your bed.
I just prefer sleeping
in a more enclosed space.
Just not too open.
This wall wasn't here originally.
It could be a large bedroom.
But you like that kind...
Yes, I like...
More sense of security.
Yes, security. Need to lock the door.
You really do love blue a lot.
I might have imagined something
very exaggerated,
an overwhelming kind of blue.
But actually,
once you enter,
you feel these blues
are used quite cleverly.
It just makes you
feel, in the subtle details,
the uniqueness and elegance of blue.
And I felt
that the overall color tone looked
very pleasing to the eye.
Immediately sensed his taste.
And this is the dining room.
Yes.
The cat.
Facai.
Its name is Facai.
Good kitty.
It's so happy.
Tired now.
Still nervous?
Much better.
Let's go wash our hands
and start preparing.
Put on an apron.
Come on.
Naturally.
Actually, she can tie it herself,
but...
They want to do it like that.
Being in a relationship means
helping each other out.
Do you want it tighter?
Not too tight.
Okay.
Rock sugar, light soy sauce.
What are you going to make now?
Making a sauce.
A Ningbo dish.
For that shrimp dish, right?
Let me take care of this side.
Okay, then you handle this soup.
Even the pots and pans are blue.
He loves blue too much.
Then I'll help you beat the eggs.
I'll beat them.
I love beating eggs the most.
Wash the eggs?
Eggs need to be washed?
Why wash eggs?
Of course.
They have chicken poop
and bacteria on the outside.
They need to be washed.
I haven't washed eggs
in over thirty years.
You've just eaten a lot of...
So sudden.
Sorry.
We seem so unsophisticated.
You've just eaten a lot of
chicken poop.
Tired?
Not tired.
Is your neck and back okay?
Pretty good.
I'll massage them for you later.
I'll beat them here.
Do you need ginger for this dish?
Yes.
Need it?
So harmonious.
This is exactly what we need.
In the kitchen,
actually, we cooperated very well.
But we hadn't discussed it beforehand.
Whoever was free,
they would go chop vegetables
or wash dishes.
It's cooked.
It smells so good.
Garlic fried wagyu.
Ate it all.
No, just two pieces.
Is it good?
Absolutely delicious.
Look at the compliments.
They are both
super good at complimenting.
They praise each other.
Smells so good.
Smells good.
Youling,
does the plating look okay like this?
What?
Why did you pour it all in?
I didn't pour it all in.
I originally wanted to lay out a row
and pour a shallow layer.
When Liu (Xu Lvyang) first went in,
she was probably
a bit nervous or awkward.
But later, when we cooked
in the state of shared life,
it was quite relaxing for her.
I was also quite happy.
Because
my ideal picture of love
is four seasons, three meals,
us two and a dog.
He has fantasized about this scene
for a long time.
That's enough.
Time to eat.
Dinner is served.
So abundant.
Cheers.
Come on, welcome.
Welcome.
Thank you for today.
My pleasure.
First meeting,
you two did all the work.
It's okay.
You eat first.
Eat a bit first.
It's okay.
Because you were busy all afternoon.
Yes.
Let me help you.
It's okay.
It's okay. We'll help ourselves.
Help yourselves, yes.
And this, too.
Okay, yours.
Thank you.
A very trendy meal.
Youling is very good at cooking.
Is he?
The first time ever.
Well,
I haven't made any of these before.
Yes, never.
What did he cook before?
Sweet and sour ribs, I remember.
Thank you.
Because Xu Lvyang doesn't
really eat pork,
so we didn't make braised pork belly
or ribs.
I like simple meals.
Yes.
I grew up eating in the cafeteria.
(You love it, you eat more.)
(You're young, you eat more.)
Yes.
Guess what kind of work she does.
Now that you mention it,
it's definitely not what I'd imagine,
like a little girl.
You can't really tell by looking.
No.
Information technology.
Anyway, it's definitely...
Seems close.
You studied engineering?
I didn't study engineering,
but my work now is related to it.
Playing video games?
Come on.
Uncle, eat more food.
That's you who play video games.
But this shows the father is relaxed.
Yes.
Just kidding.
(Silent)
A very popular industry.
Artificial intelligence?
Yes, I work in AI.
What did I say?
Information technology.
Yes, I was right.
Xu Lvyang also
dances.
She also plays the piano.
Multi-talented.
Xu Lvyang,
what kind of dance do you do?
Folk dance?
I learned folk dance and ballet
when I was young.
Ballet?
Great.
She also dances.
Yes, Youling told me.
But she
only started after retirement.
I think that's amazing.
Because
dancing is something
that requires physical coordination.
But she's bad at coordination.
Says who?
(Full auto retract)
No, it's not the coordination.
I meant,
(Listen to my explaination)
her skill is not good.
It's just that her basics are not good.
She just says,
for her dancing,
(Hurriedly explain)
her memory is good.
The teacher teaches once,
and she gets it.
That's very impressive.
And then...
Oh.
(Explaining complete)
He keeps looking at her.
For older people,
there's no requirement for flexibility.
But it requires your dance sense.
As soon as I retired, I started to
learn the basics of ballet first.
I studied for two years.
That really trains your physique.
Yes.
Let me show you my mom dancing.
This is quite impressive.
This is not basic at all.
We've even performed abroad.
That's very good.
Turning a hobby into a profession.
Yes.
Actually, it's just when you get older,
find something to do.
Staying home all day is boring.
Just find something to do.
Actually, I think
his parents make people feel
very comfortable.
Whether it's talking about my work
or my hobbies,
even their hobbies,
it felt very natural.
And
I found it interesting when listening.
I got a step closer to Youling.
Does Youling come home often?
Just recently, he's been a bit busier.
Before, yes.
He's busy.
He's renovating over there.
Renovating that place.
There's a lot to do there.
He's quite family-oriented.
Relatively speaking,
very family-oriented.
And if there's any good food
or movies,
he'll take us to try.
He told me so.
He'll take us to try them.
For any holiday,
he'll arrange everything.
Very thoughtful.
Yes, very thoughtful.
Just like the popular
kind of warm-hearted guy.
When he was little,
I took him everywhere.
Even for business trips,
I brought him along.
No wonder he's so close to his family.
His family relationships are very good.
I think Xu Lvyang
will be even happier in such a family.
Because his dad
took him everywhere,
so the family relationships are good.
He is willing to go out with us.
Yes, to go out and have fun.
For example,
with our classmates,
my friends,
sometimes we go out.
Thank you
for cooking such a sumptuous meal.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. and Mrs. Zhou.
This is really good.
So harmonious and happy.
This is my secret base.
Before,
when I was unhappy,
I would sit here alone,
watch the sunset,
and drink a bottle of beer.
Then I'd walk home.
Drink a bottle of beer?
This is my daily routine.
It's just that today,
there's one more person.
Do you like it?
Actually, walking around here
on weekends is quite nice.
Today is the weekend.
Today is Sunday.
Actually,
on most of the weekends,
my life is like this.
Walking the dog is also quite nice.
Do you usually
walk the dog in the morning or at night?
Usually, I walk myself.
Just myself.
And you?
You are a little dog?
You walk yourself alone?
I'm both a pig and a dog.
Usually...
Well, one day, I was so unhappy.
I cried right here for a long time.
On this bench.
Yes.
That day, I just sat right here.
Do you want to sit here?
Let's sit for a while.
Can you sit here?
I'll sit to your left.
How long do you usually sit here
during a walk?
From around when it's almost sunset,
I walk over,
or ride a bike for a round,
and then after riding, I go over there.
It's quite pleasant like this.
I feel that these past few days
with Lu Bingkun has been very happy.
My understanding of Lu Bingkun
has deepened a lot.
And I was thinking,
I could share
some of my own daily routines with him.
Winter is quite cold.
Now this season is just right.
In another two or three months,
go for a walk by the riverside,
take a stroll,
and also stop by my place.
We can eat something together.
"Come to my place
and we can eat something together."
Let's go.
Time to go home and cook.
I'll take this. You can wear it.
It's a bit cold. You should put it on.
It's okay.
This lock is a bit high-tech.
Only my mom's and my fingerprints.
Indeed.
(Wang Yi's home)
So,
just put it here.
We bought some groceries.
So lavish today?
Let me make you a hamburger.
Come on, help me tie this.
Help me tie it.
Tighter or looser?
Either is fine.
Do I have one?
Am I just the assistant?
You don't have one.
I'll leave it to you.
You do this.
I'll give you that.
(Headphones)
Starting to be mischievous.
(Connected again)
The earphones again. Here we go again.
Start.
First, we need to prep the ingredients.
Wash them.
The head chef is about to prepare.
I'll peel it for you.
Peel two of the most beautiful leaves
to put in that burger.
That's enough.
No more.
(Taste it)
Slice some mushrooms,
Mr. Lu.
Lu.
Roger that.
You're sneaking food, aren't you?
Your prepped ingredients are being
attacked by the back kitchen.
I feel like they could get married now.
Let me stir-fry some vegetables first.
Pour it in?
Pour it in.
Awesome.
You didn't study at a culinary school
in London, did you?
So great.
Is this a master chef?
So good at complimenting.
Is this a Michelin three-star chef?
Sweet.
Salmon, love it.
Smells so good.
Pan-fry over low heat.
That young guy there,
did he say something?
The young guy said to take it slow.
So, do you think we take it too fast?
I think it's the kind of rhythm
that is comfortable for both of us.
(Even just cooking together can...)
(I think she is)
(a person who really loves life.)
(Two people coming home from work
together,)
(having a drink, chatting,)
(and then cooking a meal together)
(is actually)
(a very warm picture of life.)
(I dream of this scene.)
Did you squeeze a heart shape?
I squeezed an abstract heart.
Alright.
This smells so good.
Smells good.
Perfect.
Cheers.
Let's start with a burger.
This cross-section
is amazing.
There's a mushroom that escaped.
I don't even want to look up to talk.
So good.
My cooking is better than dancing,
right?
You're also very talented at dancing.
But your talent for cooking
is clearly a bit better.
Delicious.
Our first beach date,
we also had burgers.
Give a review.
The two burgers are different.
That burger was eaten,
this burger is savored.
(Impressive.)
And the two people eating there,
their relationship changed a bit.
Thanks to the burger.
And thanks to the chef.
What a great compliment.
You know how to compliment.
Today, I'll make
a baby food version of mixed noodles.
Are we going to feed each other now?
Let's open a restaurant.
Today, when Lu Bingkun
sat across from me,
I suddenly remembered that day
when I was alone,
quietly eating pasta.
(When Wang Yi was home alone)
It felt like
I sent my order signal
to the universe,
that I wanted someone
to eat pasta with me,
and I must really like this person.
The universe received this signal,
and brought Lu Bingkun to me.
I felt so happy.
(I must have someone I really like)
(to eat pasta with.)
So, is this
your ideal
life after work?
Finished.
Not yet.
Rest for a bit.
I'll perform a show for you.
There's a show?
What is this?
Walking towards you.
It just performs some abstract stuff.
Did you customize this yourself?
Yes, on my birthday,
I made one for each of my friends,
and I made one for myself too.
I can also make one for you.
Make one for me.
Make two
walking forward together.
You're getting into
abstract stuff now.
On the first day we met,
you didn't dare to speak.
We could also run.
Like a running race.
Just to see who goes further.
So who usually wins this?
I'm the last one.
Why? Short legs?
My motor is just not strong enough.
I feel like cooking at home
is much more intimate.
Because when cooking in the house,
you have to consider everyone.
But when we
cook at home,
we only consider the two of us.
It feels like he and I
have known each other for a long time.
Just two people at home together,
simply cooking a meal.
This is what you call clean.
Let me show you what clean means.
It shows it's really delicious.
I wasn't just trying to make you happy.
This is really clean.
(The happiness from this)
(is more healing)
than an adrenaline rush,)
(and more grounding.)
So nice.
Ma'am, thank you.
No need for thanks.
You're so kind.
Before I came...
I really liked you.
I really like you.
I was very nervous before coming.
Really.
Auntie, you're so nice.
It's okay.
Our home
is the most relaxing place.
We don't have
parental airs or anything.
My husband is the same.
You're both so nice.
So,
if you two work out,
I hope you'll come here often.
Okay.
Youling treats me very well.
I hope you two can make it.
He's also very considerate to me.
Really.
I really like you.
I liked you at first sight.
Thank you.
I really like you too.
It's fate.
Don't worry.
If you come to our home,
you can rest assured.
Our family is...
My husband and I
absolutely...
As long as you make your own decisions,
we won't interfere in anything.
Whether it works out or not,
I will still like you.
I hope it works out.
Bless you both.
Thank you, ma'am.
You're welcome.
Whether it works out or not,
I will always like you.
This is very important.
It means I like you as a person.
Really so kind.
I was alone
chatting with his mom,
his mom was
very sincere.
I'm very grateful
for an elder to express goodwill
to a younger person
so openly and without hiding,
I felt especially touched.
I felt warmth in my heart.
This really scores a lot of points.
No wonder he wanted to bring the girl
straight home.
He knew this moment
was a huge plus.
A huge bonus.
Yes, a huge plus.
Thank you for inviting me to your home.
Cheers.
Your families are so nice.
I just chatted with your mom alone.
I saw that.
So I didn't go in.
I just heard something like,
"If it really works out..."
Stuff like that.
You heard it?
I heard
that one sentence.
I was just about to walk over,
and then I heard that.
So I came back.
You just left?
Your father is very funny.
(Before I came here,)
(I was very nervous.)
(And they made me relax a lot.)
Thank you.
I didn't lie to you.
About lying or not,
it's just that you need to
experience it to know.
(Right.)
(Because she didn't grow up like this,)
(she doesn't know)
(that a family can be like this.)
There's a fragrance.
Yes.
Smell it.
So, if you leave the house,
what's the first thing you want to do?
(Preview)
London Eye?
I stayed there for over three years,
but never rode it.
That should be ridden
with someone you love.
Right.
Yes.
This hand just can't let go anymore.
They're about to be glued together.
When I was working today,
I was completely
running out of battery.
Seeing you come, I felt like
there's a backup battery.
Backup?
A power bank?
Yes.
Why are you sitting so far away?
Girl...
I just want to watch this stage.
I like it too.
When the flirtation reaches its peak.
Then I'll sing a Chinese song first.
Go ahead.
Learning her favorite song, right?
(2 hours left until leaving the house)
The last dinner before confession.
This is the last meal.
(Make your last post before the end)
Moments segment.
Public to all.
(Moments fully public)
Make all previous ones public.
We need to read carefully.
Whose are these?
Expose your Moments.
We two seem
to have a slight misalignment.
From the first one
to the last one,
it feels like a short story.
It can't be a plot twist now, right?
Don't mess around, okay?
When you encounter unhappy things
in a relationship,
will you share them
with your other half?
Do you want to hear?
If you want to hear, I can tell you.
I think you're very handsome.
You play it very beautifully.
When I was looking at you at that time,
I thought,
how is this guy so handsome?
There was a beam of light behind you.
A beam of light
shining on you.
Don't get shy on me now.
I'm getting shy.
Entered my domain.
I like it.
This layer is the key point.
"Whether it works out or not,
I will always like you."
Sweet.
Here we go again.
You two are really hilarious.
A thousand words
turn into a finger heart.